There's a cushion that looks like a manjuu.
Isn't it?
There's a little chair, and we're facing each other.
What's going on?
Sitting down for the night. - Yeah.
Oh, yeah, dinner, right.
We're having dinner, quietly, like this.
With the temple in the back. - Oh, yeah.
Now that the show's over, we can relax.
I'm going to the bath now.
I'm going to the public bath.
There's one in the neighborhood.
I rented it.
I'll go with Omokan.
I'll go with Omote
I'm going to a public bathhouse
Here we are at the bathhouse
I'm so lost
I'm going to take a bath
It's 10 p.m. and it's open until 11 p.m.
Oh no!
Let's hurry up, I'm off!
He's cute.
Isn't that a dolphin? Dolphins.
I've been in the tub.
He's in the tub.
They're just coming out.
Hinodeyuu.
I'm so glad I slipped in!
I'm glad I slipped in just in time.
I'm so glad I made it.
It was really amazing.
It looks like something out of a TV drama
Very retro.
It was like old times.
Yeah.
It was so cute.
Wow.
And a Corona Democrat.
No, I was confused... coffee milk.
I know what you mean.
But I knew I wanted to go here.
I still want to go back.
I know, right?
Let's go to the Homo Hotel.
Let's go back to the hotel.
aph an gdzie
c два sinBut Kirair Конечно
bin
c work
ת độ
h
Both of us
It's my first time here.
I don't know, I've never been here before.
But, you know, we each come here on our own private time, right, Kyoto?
Yes, Kyoto is.
I have an impression of Kyoto.
I've been here a lot.
Why haven't I been here before?
I don't know.
It would take too much time to visit all the main places.
Yes, sometimes they are a little far away from the places you want to visit.
Yes, yes.
So, surprisingly, I thought I would visit these places again someday,
If I thought I would go to both places,
When I asked Nao about it, she said she had never been there.
I thought, "Great!
I thought you had been to Spring.
Yeah, we both thought so.
I'm glad we did.
I'm going through the circle.
I'd like to go through it solo.
We'll just have to work on our timing.
If they line up behind me, they won't be able to see me.
That's for sure, sir.
I want to go, I want to go, I want to go!
I have to dance now.
Oh, just like that.
Okay.
How do you go around?
We'll take a walk here first, and then...
I wonder if it's in the back.
Main Shrine main Shrine line
A gentle drop from the top.
Good night
Thousand torii gates
Amazing!
I'm going to take a picture.
Here...
I want to take pictures.
There must be some famous spots.
Everyone's amazing.
They were taking pictures when people were leaving, right?
That's what I'm talking about.
That's impossible.
What timing?
That's amazing.
But it's cool.
Oh, my God.
That's where it's coming from.
The street's going to be tiny.
That's where they were filming.
There's so many people.
Can I film while I'm walking?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
This one, this one, this one.
Rochein' get it!
Oh, my God.
Cute.
It's not easy to find, is it?
This one.
I like that you can put it in two places with a double spread.
Yay!
I'm in!
I didn't know there was a way out that didn't involve a torii gate!
First of all, Haru and her family ate beef cutlet, okonomiyaki, yakisoba, yakiniku, yogurt and bananas in the morning the day before yesterday.
They eat a lot.
They eat a lot. This place looks really nice. It's super beautiful.
It looks great. I want to take pictures.
It's going to be really beautiful with maple leaves in the fall.
It's so nice!
Beautiful!
So good!
We've moved to Nishiki Market.
Right in front of you now.
It's already an arcade town, and it's so nice!
I'm hungry
I'm so hungry!
I can smell all kinds of good smells!
I had a lot of ambitions before I came here.
I'm going to have a look at the stores and decide what I'm going to eat.
I'm hungry.
I want to buy something.
This is fun!
Looks delicious!
Shrimp.
Delicious!
That's a lot of seafood.
Seafood.
Seafood!
Something is...
It's a café.
It's like clouds.
It's cute.
So cute!
Looks delicious.
Delicious.
Delicious
Delicious!
This is the best!
This is great!
This is great.
Two days of live music.
Yeah, day three.
Where do you want to start? Where do you want to start? I'll start with the eggs.
I thought it was tempura.
Can you see it?
Delicious!
Looks so good!
Yellow eggs.
Delicate texture.
May I try it?
Please try it!
I want to eat it!
Wow!
This is the one I recommend with rice!
It's the best!
I love it!
I'll have some rice with it.
It's too good!
Now I want to eat it all!
I was walking and I found a place called Nishiki Tenmangu Shrine.
Let's go there!
Nishiki Tenmangu Shrine.
I'm going to take a picture as it is!
Here we are at the Kamo River.
As you can see, there is a lot of water.
It's overflowing with water.
Is there ever a sound coming from the Kamo River like this?
I don't think so.
It sounds like this.
It's a little calmer.
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
That's the Kamo River, right?
It fits. It fits.
It's the right river.
No, it's the Kamo River.
It's supposed to be calmer.
Here we are at Tennoji Temple!
Yay!
Second time at Kenninji.
Next, the second Kenninji
Subscribed at the mouth of the Zizhikou
Suddenly the place has changed
Hey, cute!
What kind of town is it?
I wonder what it's called.
It's so calm
A private alley.
I don't know.
I don't know your brother.
It's true.
What is it?
What's that?
It's like a talisman that no one else has.
I have one of those.
A seesaw thing?
Yeah, I think so.
No, no, no, that's a good one, no, no, no, that's funny.
No, no, no, no, no, that's funny.
It's funny.
When you come to the cafe, it's like an ending.
It's true, I get old.
I ordered cold green tea and lemonade for my brain.
Yeah, I'm already craving soda.
They're both cold.
What's the temperature today?
It's 30 degrees.
You're saying 30 degrees?
It's a balmy 30.
It's hot today.
It's hot.
It is.
Really.
It's a little sweet, but if it's not enough, put some in.
Mix it in and drink it.
Lemonade.
Doggy.
Kampai.
Kamperai.
Lemonade.
So lemony!
Sweet
refreshing
Delicious
It's so good!
Oh, my God.
You're doing this right now, aren't you?
I'm afraid the goddess is about to be eaten.
That's right, I'm going to eat it!
I had a full day today, so I went to Abi's Q's, and got this bear from Aveno Q's Mall.
No, a dog!
We're the characters of Cuse Mall together.
We traveled together.
He was so cute!
Oh, wow!
I love it when we go out for dinner at night.
It's great.
Oh, my God.
It's so good.
It's about this time of night.
I'm drinking wine.
I love it. - I love it.
He's so cool.
He's a foreigner.
He's so dapper.
Harajuku.
Cool.
Huge.
Huge!
Two birds.
Here they come!
Wait a minute.
What? What birds?
What is that?
What bird?
What is it?
Black and white and gray.
They're all moving in sync.
They're so synchronized.
Gan bang bang is a bird.
Kamogawa birds
There are 38 different kinds of birds.
And then the energies.
Oh, that's the Energizer!
That's it!
I don't know the name.
Oh, Osagiku.
Blue Heron.
Is this a rest stop? He's so cool!
This is Mr. Aosagi.
Come in, Aosagi.
Aosagi.
What's he doing?
Grooming.
Hey, there.
Ah!